{
  "ratio": 0.8,
  "questionCount": 10,

  "questions": [
    {
      "questionText": "What do titans start their life as?",
      "answers": ["World-souls", "World souls"]
    },
    {
      "questionText": "Where do the orcs originate from?",
      "answers": ["Draenor"]
    },
    {
      "questionText": "By what name are blood elves known as formally?",
      "answers": ["Sin'dorei"]
    },
    {
      "questionText": "Where was Dalaran located before moving to Northrend?",
      "answers": ["Hillsbrad Foothills", "Hillsbrad"]
    },
    {
      "questionText": "Who cursed the earthen and other titanic creations with the curse of flesh?",
      "answers": ["Yogg-Saron"]
    },
    {
      "questionText": "Onyxia spied on Stormwind under the guise of who?",
      "answers": ["Katrana Prestor", "Lady Katrana Prestor", "Lady Prestor"]
    },
    {
      "questionText": "Where did Thrall's Horde shipwreck before reaching Kalimdor?",
      "answers": ["Darkspear Islands"]
    },
    {
      "questionText": "Who led the Cult of the Damned during the rise of the Scourge?",
      "answers": ["Kel'Thuzad"]
    },
    {
      "questionText": "Where was the Exodar originally located before departing? (be specific)",
      "answers": ["Tempest Keep"]
    },
    {
      "questionText": "Which dragon aspect was corrupted and started the infinite dragonflight?",
      "answers": ["Nozdormu"]
    },
    {
      "questionText": "In which expansion was Thousand Needles flooded?",
      "answers": ["Cataclysm"]
    },
    {
      "questionText": "Which swamp was turned into a wasteland over time?",
      "answers": ["Black Morass"]
    },
    {
      "questionText": "Who became the Lich King after the downfall of Arthas?",
      "answers": ["Bolvar Fordragon", "Bolvar", "Fordragon"]
    },
    {
      "questionText": "Who was Medivh's apprentice?",
      "answers": ["Khadgar"]
    },
    {
      "questionText": "Who possessed Medivh before his untimely death?",
      "answers": ["Sargeras"]
    },
    {
      "questionText": "What were Gilean druids originally referred as?",
      "answers": ["Harvest Witches"]
    }
  ]
}
